The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The rank 1000 Demon Spirit Crystal
Rank 1000\NDemon Spirit Crystal
can be converted into celestial spiritual energy.
But even if I add all the celestial jades I have,
it would barely be enough to reach Late stage Soul Transformation.
Halt, intruder !
I have important matters to discuss with your Commander Wang.
The Ancestor is in seclusion,
please come back later.
Fellow cultivator Yao, barging in rudely like this
isn't very polite.
Sorry for being rude.
I hope fellow cultivator Wang will forgive me
but I really have an urgent request.
If it's not worth my time,
then don't blame me for being impolite too.
Fellow cultivator Wang,
this matter is extremely confidential
so I need to be on guard.
I hope you don't mind.
This whole Demon Spirit Land
used to be the cultivation cave of a Celestial.
After the collapse of the Celestial Realm,
it stopped being used.
I accidentally found a path to that celestial cave
but I can't break the restrictions outside it alone.
I heard fellow cultivator Wang is skilled in restrictions.
If we successfully enter,
we will split the celestial artifacts inside equally between us.
What do you think ?
A celestial cave is indeed worth exploring.
But this person isn't trustworthy.
I need to inquire a bit more...
I'm at a critical point in my cultivation.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
I presume fellow cultivator Wang is trying to breakthrough to Late stage
but doesn't have enough celestial jades.
To show my sincerity,
I am willing to provide fellow cultivator Wang
with enough celestial jades to reach Early stage Ascendant.
This is the deposit,
it should be enough to help you reach Late stage Soul Transformation.
I will give you the rest
if we
succeed in entering the cave.
As expected of the Blood Ancestor's daughter...
She really is extravagant.
This is too dangerous,
I'm sorry but I'm not willing to take the risk.
If fellow cultivator Wang is worried about safety,
you can take this Blood Soul Pill.
It will ensure your safety.
A Blood Soul Pill !?
This pill is refined by the Blood Ancestor's secret technique.
I've heard that even your body is completely destroyed
and your Origin Soul crushed,
you can still use this pill to reconstruct them
and be completely unharmed.
If I obtain such a life-saving treasure,
I would be able to escape deadly situations.
I've heard of this, it's the Blood Planet's treasure...
How is this pill used ?
This is my Yao Family's secret,
I can't reveal it so easily
unless... you agree to come with me.
I'll even give you one more
as payment.
Agreed.
Use the method in this jade
to leave a mark on the Blood Soul Pill.
It will link your body and Origin Soul to the pill
to allow you to reconstruct your body and soul.
Let's meet in 3 days
at the hour the purple demon rises
on top of Drum Mountain.
When I hold this pill,
it feels like we share the same blood.
3 days later
I'm going out for a bit.
While I'm away,
you two will stay in the Black Armor Barracks and wait for me.
Remember to cultivate.
Understood !
Drum Mountain\NDemon Spirit Land
I've given him enough celestial jades
but after 3 days
he still hasn't reached Late stage Soul Transformation.
It seems he isn't very talented.
When the purple demon reaches its peak,
a ray of blood-colored light will come from the compass.
Follow me closely.
Celestial Qing Lin's cave\NDemon Spirit Land
Focus your mind and sit here,
concentrate on your domain.
Once recognized by the golden symbol,
we will walk the Revered Dragon Path.
The golden energy entered her body ?
Your turn now.
Yao Xixue's body
now gives off the pressure of a Celestial.
I only got a 3-strokes golden symbol.
He actually obtained at least 6 !
Could it be that his domain is superior to mine ?
How is that possible ?
Let's go.
Yao Xixue is very familiar with this place,
it's clearly not her first time entering.
As the Blood Ancestor's beloved daughter,
she should have all the celestial artifacts she needs.
Why does she risk coming here ?
First platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Her obsession with this celestial cave
must be because of the Blood Ancestor's orders.
She must have other objectives.
This place has 12 layers of restrictions,
we will take turns breaking them.
I'll take the first layer.
Seal !
This statue's cultivation is no less than Soul Transformation.
Can Yao Xixue seal it so easily ?
Artifacts from the Blood Planet really are something...
This is...
A golden symbol ?
The golden symbol in the statue
is almost identical to the one I just gained from my domain.
Could it be that these golden symbols made of celestial spiritual energy
were sealed inside the statues ?
If that's true,
these 12 layers of restrictions aren't obstacles
but an incredible opportunity !
Second platform\NRevered Dragon Path
If it's really made of restrictions
then there must be a way to lift them !
With his skill in restrictions, he should be able to break it directly.
Why is he fighting with the statue ?
As I thought.
This is the restriction's core.
Release !
Why is there a golden symbol inside the statue !?
This golden symbol
seems to have one more stroke than the one on the first platform.
It was an accident.
He just got lucky, that's all.
Third platform\NRevered Dragon Path
I just need to smash the statue,
what's so difficult about it ?
This time it has 3 strokes.
How exactly did I fail ?
Why aren't there any golden symbols !?
Fourth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
A 4-strokes golden symbol...
As I thought.
Fifth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
How exactly did he do it ?
Sixth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Seventh platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Eighth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Ninth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Tenth platform\NRevered Dragon Path
Eleventh platform\NRevered Dragon Path
This is the last one,
a 12-strokes golden symbol...
This is...
the character 'Lin' ?
I am Qing Lin.
It seems the former owner of this cave was named Qing Lin.
Something's wrong...
These 12 layers of restrictions...
kept increasing in difficulty.
But with Yao Xixue's strength,
she could easily pass through just by using her artifacts.
Why did she insist on inviting me then ?
The restriction statues aren't the final challenge.
This place...
has other dangers.
Ferocious wind blocks the path.
We have no way back.
If you can survive 3 strikes,
you qualify to enter the cave.
We'll each take a strike,
and survive the last one together.
Gentleman,
you're first.
Step forward now.
Fellow cultivator Wang,
please.
And if I refuse ?
As you can see,
the way back is blocked.
All who have obtained a golden symbol
must enter the celestial cave in order to survive.
So...
inviting me to break restrictions was just a pretense.
The real reason was to have me take the strikes for you ?
We just need to withstand these 3 Ascendant level sword strikes together
and we can enter the celestial cave.
Fellow cultivator Yao flatters me.
I'm only at Middle stage Soul Transformation,
how can I withstand Ascendant level sword strikes ?
Wang Lin,
blocking the strikes with me
is your only path to survival.
Succeed and live
or fail and die.
You...
have no choice.
Don't worry,
didn't you already take the Blood Soul Pill ?
Fellow cultivator Yao is quite the schemer.
Likewise.
I hope you will
keep your promise.
With your Middle stage Soul Transformation cultivation,
taking a sword strike
won't necessarily kill you.
Use the Blood Soul Pill's spell now !
You must survive fellow cultivator Wang !
But if you took the fake pill I gave you...
you will die for sure...
The location of this celestial cave
is the ultimate secret of my Yao Family.
How could I let you leave alive ?
Wang Lin,
it should be an honor to sacrifice yourself
for the Yao Family.
The first strike
can be considered blocked.
Are you ready
for the second strike ?
Bring it on !
I entered this place several times.
The statue restrictions
can be passed using artifacts.
But for these 3 sword strikes,
I could only block the first 2.
Now that Wang Lin blocked one for me,
I'm sure I can win.
The final strike.
Father...
I didn't fail to meet your expectations !
I did it !
The Yao Family
might finally ascend !
Thank you fellow cultivator Yao,
for blocking 2 strikes for me.
You're still alive !?
I suspected all along
that the Blood Soul Pill you gave me was fake.
How could you have given
such a precious treasure to me so easily ?
And you were so concerned about my safety
that you used your Divine Sense
to ensure I took the pill.
If the pill was fake,
then the celestial cave was most likely real.
So I didn't use the celestial jades you gave me to breakthrough.
Instead, I converted them into a celestial crystal and stored it within my body
to use it to save my life.
So you used this celestial crystal to withstand the Ascendant sword strike
and then used the impact to pretend falling in the abyss.
Then you waited for me to withstand 2 strikes
and be weakened
to strike back...
Zhou Wutai told me
that the true use of the straw hat is to conceal your aura.
Don't waste your energy,
I've already sealed your meridians.
Right now, you...
can't even use celestial spiritual energy.
Wang Lin !
You can just kill me !
Kill you ?
I'm sure you took a Blood Soul Pill.
Killing you would just let you return to some blood formation.
But if I use my Life and Death Domain to imprison you,
it won't kill you
and your Blood Soul Pill becomes completely useless...
You !
This woman laid a death trap for me
by using these Ascendant level sword strikes
and the fake Blood Soul Pill.
What kind of celestial treasure is in this cave
to make her go though so much effort ?
The remnant soul of the celestial cave
welcomes Master.
This is the celestial cave token.
Holding this token allows free entry and exit from the cave.
Master,
please enter the cave.
This token is almost identical
to the one I saw in the Tide Abyss...
Master of this celestial cave ?
No wonder.
Inside Qing Lin's Celestial Cave\NDemon Spirit Land
It's similar to palaces of the Celestial Realm...
It's entirely made of celestial jades...
The restrictions here operate both as a whole
and individually.
It must be legendary celestial restrictions...
With my current knowledge,
I can't see through any of them.
It seems there was another Master of this place before me.
This technique...
Could it be the 18 Plum Blossom Restriction from the ancient cultivation world !?
Although my predecessor already drank most of the wine,
there are still 10 drops left.
This celestial wine
is definitely no ordinary thing.
The celestial wine is mellow...
It can even intoxicate the Origin Soul...
At the time, I didn't expect
that this intoxication
would last a full year.
Time passed by. Wang Lin continued to cultivate at the Black Armor Barracks. After absorbing the demonic spiritual energy of more than 500 demon soldiers and Regiment Leader Sun, the demon crystal in his body broke past rank 1000 when he finally fused them all.\N\NAbsorbing demonic spiritual energy with a rank 1000 plus demon crystal was several times faster than before.\N\NWang Lin didn’t care about any of the matters in the military camp. He spent all his time absorbing demonic spiritual energy to prepare for breaking into the late stage of Soul Transformation.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?